Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXVIII is arranged in 24 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXVIII. INTERSTATE COMMERCE COMMISSION
  - Sub-Series 276-0. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Dockets, 1938-1939 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - General, 1961 (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - General. Union Tank Car Company, 1958-1961 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      June 1958-61.
    - Copies of Briefs to ICC Case #MC67916, 1961 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - General. Accident Reports. Form T, 1956-1957 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - General. Accident Bulletin, 1941 (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - General. Parmelee Transportation Company, 1952-1956 (Box 254, Folder 8)
      April 26, 1952-56.
    - General. Parmelee Transportation Company, 1950-1952 (Box 254, Folder 9)
      1950-April 25, 1952.
    - General, 1956 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      April 4, 1956-August 1, 1956.
    - General, 1954-1956 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      July 1954-April 3, 1956.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      November 1953-June 1954.
    - General, 1953 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      July-October 1953.
    - General, 1952-1953 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      April 1952-June 1953.
    - General, 1951-1952 (Box 255, Folder 6)
      November 1951-March 1952.
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 255, Folder 7)
      December 1950-October 1951.
    - General, 1950 (Box 255, Folder 8)
      June-November 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 255, Folder 9)
      December 1949-April 17, 1950.
    - General, 1950 (Box 255, Folder 10)
      April 18, 1950-May 1950.
    - General, 1949 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      March-November 1949.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      November 1948-February 1949.
    - General, 1948 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      1948 October
    - General, 1945-1948 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      1945-September 1948.
    - General, 1933-1944 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - General, 1921-1931 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - General, 1964 (Box 256, Folder 7)
      July 21, 1964-December 1964.
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 256, Folder 8)
      November 1963-July 20, 1964.
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 256, Folder 9)
      August 1962-October 1963.
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 256, Folder 10)
      December 4, 1958-March 1959.
    - General, 1958 (Box 256, Folder 11)
      October 1958-December 3, 1958.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 256, Folder 12)
      September 1957-September 1958.
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      September 1956-August 1957.
    - General, 1956 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      August 2-31, 1956.
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      April 1959-November 25, 1960.
    - General, 1961 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      November 26, 1960-July 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 276-1. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1945-1947 (Box 257, Folder 6)
      November 1945-47.
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1948 (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1928-1931 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1923-1927 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1920-1922 (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - 276-1(a). Rulings, Orders, etc., 1933-1945 (Box 257, Folder 11)
      1933-October 1945.
    - 276-1(b). Rulings, Orders, etc. Ex Parte No. 72 (Sub No. 1). Union Pacific Railroad Company and Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company, 1944-1948 (Box 257, Folder 12)
      August 1944-48.
    - Rulings, Orders, etc. ICC Service Orders, 1949-1952 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      November 1949-52.
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1960-1961 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      September 22, 1960-July 1961.
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1959-1960 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      1959-September 21, 1960.
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1956-1958 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Rulings, Orders, etc. Railway Express Agency MC 66562, 1957-1958 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      1957-April 1958.
    - Rulings, Orders, etc., 1949-1955 (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 276-2. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Hearings and Briefs, 1934-1951 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Hearings and Briefs, 1921-1928 (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 276-3. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Legislation, 1921-1932 (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 276-4. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Reports, 1934-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - 276-4(b). Reports. Bureau of Locomotive Inspection, 1936-1946 (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1928-1936 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1921-1931 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 276-5. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Valuation of Railroads, 1923-1932 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 276-6. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Wage Statistics Conference, 1920-1935 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 276-7. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Hearing on Efficiency and Economy of Management, 1938 (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 276-8. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Transportation of Household Goods for Express Employees, 1926-1931 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 276-9. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - US Railroad Labor Board. Decisions 2460 and 2652. El Paso and Southwestern Railway Company (Box 259, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 276-10. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Classification of Bureau Employees, 1927-1937 (Box 259, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 276-11. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Personnel, 1945-1959 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Personnel, 1936-1945 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Personnel, 1933-1934 (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - Personnel, 1929-1930 (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - Personnel, 1927-1928 (Box 259, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 276-11?. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Ex Parte No. 72 (Sub No. 1), 1938 (Box 259, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 276-12. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1934 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1933 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1932 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1931 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1929-1930 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Consolidation of Railroads. Section 1, 1930 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Consolidation of Railroads. Section 2, 1930 (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1930 (Box 260, Folder 8)
      1930 April
    - Consolidation of Railroads, 1930 (Box 260, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 276-15. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Application of Railroads for Increase in Tariff Rates, 1955-1959 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Application of Railroads for Increase in Tariff Rates, 1951-1954 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      April 1951-54.
    - Application of Railroads for Increase in Tariff Rates, 1949-1951 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      October 1949-March 1951.
    - Application of Railroads for Increase in Tariff Rates, 1948-1949 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      1948-September 1949.
    - Application of Railroads for Increase in Tariff Rates, 1937-1947 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Application of Railroads for Increase in Tariff Rates, 1931-1946 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 276-16. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Transportation of Household Effects. Railway Employees, 1933 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 276-17. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Laws Affecting, 1935 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 276-18. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Proposed Revision of Tariff System, 1936-1946 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - 276-18(b). Proposed Revision of Tariff System, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 276-19. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Railway Investments in Highway Motor Vehicle Enterprises, 1936 (Box 261, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 276-20. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Bureau of Statistics, 1936-1946 (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 276-21. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Investigation on Carloading and Freight Forwarding, 1938-1948 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Investigation on Carloading and Freight Forwarding, 1940 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Questionnaires, 1939 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 276-22. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Regulations Governing Sizes and Weights of Motor Vehicles, 1940-1941 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Regulations Governing Sizes and Weights of Motor Vehicles, 1940 (Box 262, Folder 3-4)
  - Sub-Series 276-23. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Statistics on Employment according to groups, 1944-1946 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Statistics on Employment, 1943-1946 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 276-25. Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Investigation of Passenger Fares, 1958-1959 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Investigation of Passenger Fares, 1956-1957 (Box 262, Folder 8)